Guide to the New York State Veterinary Medical Society Auxiliary records, 1948-2000
New York State Veterinary Medical Society Auxiliary records, 1948-2000
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State Veterinary Medical Society Auxiliary records, 1948-2000
6600
New York State Veterinary Medical Society Auxiliary
2.1 cubic ft.
Scrapbooks and subject files.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Scrapbooks and subject files kept by the New York State Veterinary Medical Society Auxiliary from 1948-2000.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The New York State Veterinary Medical Society Auxiliary is a women's organization affiliated with the New York State Veterinary Medical Society.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Scrapbooks and subject files kept by the New York State Veterinary Medical Society Auxiliary from 1948-2000.
Includes reports, correspondence and financial files.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State Veterinary Medical Society
Subjects:
Women--Societies and clubs.
Form and Genre Terms:
Scrapbooks
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIAL
The New York State Veterinary Medical Society records RMC # 2541
CONTAINER LIST
- 1948-1967 Scrapbook (folder 1) (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1948-1967 Scrapbook (folder 2) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 1948-1967 Scrapbook (folder 3) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1967-1971 Scrapbook (folder 1) (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 1967-1971 Scrapbook (folder 2) (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 1967-1971 Scrapbook (folder 3) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 1967-1971 Scrapbook (folder 4) (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1972-1974 Scrapbook (folder 1 ) (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 1972-1974 Scrapbook (folder 2 ) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 1972-1974 Scrapbook (folder 3 ) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 1972-1974 Scrapbook (folder 4) (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 1975-1977 Scrapbook (folder 1) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 1975-1977 Scrapbook (folder 2) (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 1975-1977 Scrapbook (folder 3) (Box 1, Folder 14)
- 1975-1977 Scrapbook (folder 4) (Box 1, Folder 15)
- 1974-1982 Scrapbook (Box 1, Volume 1)
- 1983-1992 Scrapbook (folder 1) (Box 1, Folder 16)
- 1983-1992 Scrapbook (folder 2) (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 1993-1999 Scrapbook (folder 1) (Box 2, Folder 2)
- 1993-1999 Scrapbook (folder 2) (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Auxiliary Newsletter, 1977-2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Historian's Files, 1971-1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Historian's Files, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Historian's Files, 1978-1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Historian's Files, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Historian's Files, 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Historian's Files, 1994-1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Historian's Files, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- AVMA Auxiliary (Box 3, Folder 4)
- AVMA Auxiliary Citations, 1977-1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Long Island Veterinary Medical Association Auxiliary, ca. 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Robert and Marjorie Lopez - work with mistreated horses and SPCA, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Photographs (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Programs and certificates (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Minutes and miscellany, 1983-2007 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Expenses, annual reports, etc., 1989-2007 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, reports, minutes, publications, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, reports, minutes, publications, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, reports, minutes, publications, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, reports, minutes, publications, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, reports, minutes, publications, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, reports, minutes, publications, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Financial Statements, 1985-1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Centennial Room, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 9)